A Guide to the Records of Christ Episcopal Church, 1836-1970
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Records of Christ Episcopal Church, 1836-1970
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9682
This collection contains 31 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the Library by Rev. Francis M. Cooper, Christ Church, on March 12, 1971.
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains a list of communicants, 1893-1894, 1897-1898, 1899, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1905 and index, vestry records, 1838-1933, 1940-1949, 1950-1970, marriage register, 1932-1950, church service registers, 1949-1962, parish registers, 1836-1950, minutes and correspondence about St. Anne's school, 1903-1953, register of church services, 1941-1949, and treasurer's records, 1930-1963.
Contents List
- Parish Register 1836-1887, 2 volumes (Box 1)
- Vestry Minutes/List of Communicants 1869-1871, 1875 1868-1881 (Box 1)
- Vestry Minutes 1889-1901 (Box 1)
- Vestry Minutes 1901-1908 (Box 2)
- Vestry Records 1908-1926, 2 volumes (Box 2)
- Vestry Records 1927-1933 (Box 3)
- Vestry Records 1933-1940 (Box 4)
- Treasurer's Records/1864-66 Vestry Minutes 1853-1879 (Box 4)
- Treasurer's Records 1935-1954 (Box 4)
- Register of Church Services 1949-1962, 4 volumes (Box 5)
- Minutes of the Board's Stockholders of St. Anne's School 1910-1923 (Box 5)
- Folder of Miscellaneous Correspondence 1924-1925 (Box 5)
- Vestry Minutes 1838-1895, Loose Volume
- Treasurer's Records 1930-1963, 4 Loose Volumes
- St. Anne's School Board Records 1924-1953, Loose Volume